Elevate your experience of war with the soaring air combat game Tom Clancy's H.A.W.X, finally coming on your iPhone and iPod touch!
The console hit now lands on your device:
“It is the most impressive and innovative flight-based videogame we’ve seen in years” (OPM), “a worthy addition to the best in the Clancy stable.” (Game Informer)
“Everything from the picture-perfect planes to the stunning real world environments looks great” (1UP)

**********

THE FAMOUS LICENCE NOW ON YOUR iPHONE, combining the console game's depth and quality with twisted plots and universe based on Tom Clancy's novels. Play as David Crenshaw, an elite pilot working for a powerful private military company.

13 MISSIONS TO PUT YOUR PILOT SKILLS TO THE TEST with diverse objectives and gameplay: engage aircraft in dogfights, infiltrate an enemy base, protect your allies, bomb strategic locations, provide support to ground troops and more!

26 LICENSED PLANES modeled in 3D. As an elite jet fighter, take control of the F-14A Tomcat, Mirage 2000C, F-117 Nighthawk, Eurofighter Typhoon and others. Choose the best aircraft depending on your objectives and the plane's specific characteristics. 

FULL-3D ENVIRONMENTS, based on GeoEye® satellite imagery: Fly over 13 real locations, like Rio de Janeiro or Los Angeles by night, fight in the sky of a Middle East's desert or over the Pentagon and White House in Washington.

ACCELEROMETER OR VIRTUAL JOYSTICK, choose the control mode that best fits your way of piloting. Select the cockpit view to be at the core of action or the outside view to make the best tactical choices and avoid missiles more easily.

LOCAL MULTIPLAYER MODE for up to 4 players via local Wi-Fi or Bluetooth. Death Match or Team Death Match, prepare for battle.

Destroy enemy jets, choppers, tanks, destroyers and more 40,000 feet above the earth. Enjoy the iTunes library access if you want to listen to your own music while saving the country!
Hold your breath, throttle up, push your aircraft to its limits and have your adrenaline rush!


Also available from Gameloft this Christmas: Driver, Skater Nation, James Cameron’s Avatar and N.O.V.A. – Near Orbit Vanguard Alliance.

*** Follow Gameloft on Twitter to get more info about this game and all our upcoming titles: http://twitter.com/gameloft or go read our official blog: http://blog.gameloft.com/ ***