The infection is spreading and fear is everywhere in this non-stop survival shooter. 
Head to South America as a soldier and reporter try to uncover the origin of another zombie outbreak.

12 LEVELS OF FEAR
Survive 12 levels in Campaign mode as you fight your way through favelas, mines, a zoo, docks, a boat and secret lab.

KILL ‘EM WITH STYLE
You can finish off weakened zombies with brutal and amazing fatalities by touching the action icon at just the right time. 

WATCH YOUR BACK
Switch between 2 characters, ex-soldier Damien Sharpe and reporter Alex Rayne, as they fight together to survive and uncover an evil plot.

MANY FORMS OF EVIL
Fight countless enemies of all shapes and sizes, including mutants & infected animals, each with unique abilities

UNCOVER THE STORY
Discover the full depth of the intrigue as you discover the source of the infection and the plans of the ones who created it.

IMMERSIVE VISUALS
Every environment and character is meticulously rendered in full in 3D so you can feel as close to the action as possible without starting your own zombie outbreak.

Unlock 20 trophies and show them off to friends over Gameloft LIVE!
--------------------------------------------------------------------------
Also available from Gameloft: Brothers In Arms 2®: Global Front, N.O.V.A. – Near Orbit Vanguard Alliance, GT Racing: Motor Academy, James Cameron’s Avatar, Modern Combat: Sandstorm, Driver, Tom Clancy’s H.A.W.X.

*** Follow Gameloft on Twitter to get more info about this game and all our upcoming titles at http://twitter.com/gameloft or go read our official blog at http://blog.gameloft.com/ ***