The highly acclaimed Brothers in Arms series returns for its most compelling battle yet amidst the fires of WWII.

Try out Brothers in Arms® 2: Global Front FREE and take part in a mission in the Pacific.

--------------------------------------------------------------------------
FULL VERSION KEY FEATURES:

JOIN YOUR ALLIES ONLINE
For the first time, challenge up to 5 friends to multiplayer battles on a variety of five maps in 3 different modes (Free For All, Team Deathmatch, Domination). You can connect locally via Bluetooth or even go online with Wi-Fi to battle friends anywhere.

A FIGHT ACROSS THE GLOBE
Experience every front of the war with battles raging across 5 locations and 13 levels: Pacific, Normandy, North Africa, Germany, Sicily.

WAR MACHINES
Take control of 3 different vehicles including the tank, off-road vehicle or glider to overrun your opponents - or to make a daring escape. You can even jump behind the vehicle turret to lay waste to foes with the machine gun.

THE BATTLE COMES TO LIFE
The stunning graphics and authentic settings are inspired by real life battlefields from WWII and created in detailed 3D.

AN EPIC EXPERIENCE
Witness compelling cinematic moments with more interaction between you and your squad members that deepens the gameplay.

AN ARSENAL AT YOUR DISPOSAL
Grab a wide variety of historically accurate weapons including machine guns, bazookas, sniper rifles and flamethrowers.

Unlock 26 trophies and show them off to friends over Gameloft LIVE!
--------------------------------------------------------------------------
Also available from Gameloft: N.O.V.A. – Near Orbit Vanguard Alliance, GT Racing: Motor Academy, James Cameron’s Avatar, Modern Combat: Sandstorm, Driver, Tom Clancy’s H.A.W.X.

*** Follow Gameloft on Twitter to get more info about this game and all our upcoming titles at http://twitter.com/gameloft or go read our official blog at http://blog.gameloft.com/ ***
