Grooooovy! One of the all-time most iconic video game characters is now coming to iPhone & iPod touch!

-------------------------------------------
PocketGamer: 8/10  + Silver Award - “It's a first-class conversion of one of the all-time great games”

Touch Arcade: ""One of the best looking and sounding versions of the game""
-------------------------------------------

Live or re-live the freaky adventures of Earthworm Jim in a refreshing remake of the classic action/platform game.

Jim was an ordinary earthworm who did very earthworm-like things. One day, during a battle in outer-space, a suit dropped to Earth and landed on Jim, mutating him into a large and intelligent (at least by earthworm standards) superhero. When Jim learns of the evil plans of Psy-Crow and Queen Slug-for-a-Butt, he decides to rescue Princess What's-Her-Name.

FULL VERSION FEATURES:

Play as the grooviest earthworm in the galaxy, and explore a crazy universe that offers huge gameplay possibilities:

- Run, gun, swing from hooks with your head, launch cows, bungee jump, rocket through speed levels and more.
- Face 12 types of enemies and 9 bosses.
- 4 different styles of gameplay: Side-scrolling run & gun, space racing, bungee jumping and underwater levels
- 10 original environments divided into 16 levels
- 4 levels of difficulty – including the challenging mode of the original game
- The re-mastered cult soundtrack
- iPod library access to play your favorite tracks while playing the game.

Follow us on Twitter for more information: www.twitter.com/EarthwormjimHD
