Try out the lite version of James Cameron’s Avatar™ and embark on a fantastic journey of redemption and discovery two decades prior to the film’s events. As the first experimental avatar, experience the amazing powers your new body bestows. Will you use those powers to save the Na’vi, or will you work with the humans to destroy their world?
*** ""This game is one all action fans must own."" - Slide To Play, 4/4 
*** “The graphics of Avatar are impressive, and show Gameloft's continued efforts to push the limits of the platform.” – Preview by TouchArcade
*** “It's solid and impressive so far. Gameloft put a lot of work into this game, pushing it past your typical movie license game. It shows that they care about what they're releasing, even for a phone game.” – Preview by Destructoid

Full version features:

THE STORY THAT CAME BEFORE
Uncover an original story that takes place two decades prior to the film and learn how the first avatar came to be.

FROM PANDORA'S ROOTS TO THE SKY
Go on a journey of exploration, danger and adventure in an unimaginable world. Fight for survival in tense action sequences against ferocious beasts and carnivorous plants. When the battle reaches its height, take to the skies of Pandora on a banshee in epic shoot‘em-up sequences.

DEFEND THE NA’VI
Join the Na’vi in their native village. Help protect their world by accepting their missions to fight against and conquer the human invaders.

A WORLD FULL OF WONDER
Explore every aspect of Pandora, the world created by James Cameron. Discover 15 levels, from the human-built mines and military strongholds to beautiful waterfalls and lush jungles that come alive at night with bioluminescent plants.

EVERY WEAPON AT YOUR DISPOSAL
Discover Na’vi fighting techniques. Train your precision as you master the bow, and perform combos with your fighting staff. You can also master human weaponry including high-powered guns.

THE VOICE OF NEYTIRI
The voice of Neytiri in the movie narrates the epic story

----------------------------------------------------

Return to Pandora on Blu-ray & DVD April 22

Become a fan of Gameloft on Facebook: www.facebook.com/gameloft
Follow us on Twitter: www.twitter.com/gameloft 

Published and developed by Gameloft.
