Rayman, the world-famous video game icon, is back and ready for action! Relive all the enjoyment of Rayman 2: The Great Escape, the game that brought the armless hero into 3D environments for the first time!

FULL GAME FEATURES:

45 FULLY 3D ENVIRONMENTS:
For the first time in an iPhone/iPod Touch platform game, every environment is fully rendered in 3D!
Explore waterfalls, deep sea caves, and pirate hideouts 

RESCUE RAYMAN’S WORLD
Ruthless pirates have invaded the Glades of Dreams to capture and enslave Rayman's friends. 
Your mission: to free Rayman's friends and reap the reward of their magical powers, defeat barbaric pirates and gather the four masks of Polokus.

MULTIPLE TYPES OF GAMEPLAY
Help Rayman run, climb, swim, water-ski and even fly with his helicopter hair. 
Use the virtual stick to control Rayman in all directions and activate his magical powers!

A FAST-PACED ADVENTURE
Follow the road to victory by flying rockets, riding whirlwinds and surfing on lava streams 
Dozens of hours of fun you can take even further by collecting all 1,000 hidden lums scattered across the levels!
