Get hooked on the FREE version of Fishing Kings and experience the most immersive and intense fishing game on iPhone/iPod Touch!

FULL VERSION KEY FEATURES

- 15 beautiful fishing spots to visit worldwide, from the Bahamas to the Amazon River
- 33 different species to catch, including marlins, golden dorados and piranhas 
- A never-before-seen underwater camera on the iPhone for an even more thrilling fishing experience 
- Make the biggest catch and unlock achievements in your Gameloft LIVE! profile or show off your fishing skills by posting your scores on the game’s leaderboards 
- An intense and realistic game thanks to a wide range of techniques and options and a huge tackle box

***************************************************************************

Become a fan of Gameloft on Facebook: gameloft.com/facebook
Follow the official Twitter account: @Gameloft
Also available from Gameloft: Rayman 2: The Great Escape, Brother in Arms® 2: Global Front, Pocket Chef, James Cameron’s Avatar and GT Racing: Motor Academy 

Published and distributed by Gameloft.

