**3 ACTION GAMES FOR 1 REDUCED PRICE!**
Action heroes wanted! If you can never get enough action, if you’re always thirsting for a good fight, this is the pack for you! Lift your sword & challenge the gods in Hero of Sparta; storm the beaches of World War II in Brothers in Arms: Hour of Heroes; and grab your weapon of choice for the brutal fighting game, Blades of Fury. This 3-in-1 deal is available only with the Gameloft Action Pack for iPhone & iPod touch, NOW FOR ONE LOW PRICE! 

“[Hero of Sparta is] a thrilling action game loaded with cinematic flair.” – IGN  
“Believe us when we say that Blades of Fury looks amazing.” – Slide to Play
“Brothers in Arms: Hour of Heroes looks to bring the fast-paced play of World War II shooters to the iPhone” – Kotaku

Hero of Sparta
Defy the gods as a Spartan hero on an epic odyssey.

- A total 360° experience: move and fight freely in 3D through the 8 majestic levels
- Face legions of enemies and the most phenomenal mythical creatures from Cerberus to the Cyclops!
- 5 weapons to upgrade and fabulous items to collect. Draw your faithful sword, axe, bow, or twin blades!
- iPhone-specific controls: Move with the virtual analogue stick and unleash his power with touch screen combos.

Blades of Fury
Prove your bravery & establish your own fighting style through brutal 1-on-1 battles.

- 10 characters, each with their own unique weapons, combos and back stories.
- 4 single-player game modes: Story, Arcade, Survival, and Practice
- Multiplayer mode for duels with friends via local Wi-Fi or Bluetooth connection
- Access to your personal music library (with OS 3.0 or higher): Play any music stored on your device during the game

Brothers in Arms
Join the 101st Airborne in the most intense WWII battles across multiple fronts:

 - The iPhone version of the world-famous Brothers in Arms franchise
 - 14 missions in 3 campaigns: Normandy, Ardennes & Tunisia
 - Unbelievable 3D graphics recreating the atmosphere of a Hollywood WWII blockbuster
 - Drive a 4x4 vehicle or a Sherman tank and use a wide range of weapons (bazooka, sniper rifle, machine guns, etc.)