Looking for a game to let off steam?
Discover one of the most addictive castle defense games on the App Store: now with amazing 3D graphics!
Feed the dark elves to the hydra, make warlocks explode against the fortress, drop a giant troll on a goblin squad, smash elves to the ground, shake away skeletons, throw boars in the air, and use magical spells to petrify, freeze or burn threatening invaders! Relentless hordes of mythical creatures are pouring out of the darkness and heading straight to your castle. With each wave, their numbers and strength grow as they get closer to breaking in! Your fingertip will become the most powerful weapon of all as you draw a zigzag on the screen to throw lightning or trace a V to trigger a tornado! Challenge your friends online to beat your achievements on Gameloft LIVE!
It’s fast. It’s fun. It’s highly addictive!