Grab a club, take a swing, and pray for a birdie! 
It's time for you to become a big hitter and drive for the green with Let's Golf! 

- 63 holes in 4 distinct locations remodelled in 3D: Fiji Beach, the American Mountains, the English Countryside, and Scottish Lochs.

- 4 cool and animated characters customizable with your own style. Each player has unique strengths and weaknesses.

- Show your friends who the best player is through Local Wi-Fi Multiplayer modes.

- Controls adaptable to anyone: Advanced mode plays like a sports simulation game and you can even add spin to the ball. Casual mode for easy fun and fewer bogies (but no, it won't let you cheat).