Let the Warrior Within take over your iPhone/iPod touch! One of the most anticipated video game franchises is finally available on the App Store. Hunted down by the Empress of Time, you’ll embark on a pirate ship and visit accursed palaces to triumph over evil. 

A CONSOLE-QUALITY GAME
** Graphics optimized to push the technical capabilities of the iPhone.
** Enjoy an explosive mixture of intense fighting moves for an impressive level of quality for character animations.
** All the cinematics and voices from the console version will make you experience a great adventure in a fascinating world. 

AN ICONIC VIDEO GAME SERIES
One of the most famous and anticipated video game franchises is finally on your iPhone/iPod touch in the Warrior Within edition that was acclaimed by critics and players when released on console. 

A LONG PATH TO MAKE THE GOOD TRIUMPH 
** 12 beautiful chapters in ancient palaces sheltering dozens of enemies 
** Many enigmas and sinister traps to outsmart 

LET THE WARRIOR WITHIN TAKE YOU OVER 
Utilize the environment, numerous weapons, and your enemies themselves to develop your own unique fighting style and enjoy a great freedom in your moves. 

A DARK AND VIOLENT ATMOSPHERE
** Hunted down by the Empress of Time, you will have to confront your destiny alone, fight legions of enemies and face all the ancient fears of humanity to survive. Embark on a pirate ship or visit accursed palaces and triumph over evil. 
** Explore a mysterious island with fascinating environments that will immerse you in a thrilling gaming experience.

***************************************************************************
Follow Gameloft on Twitter to get more info about this game and all our upcoming titles at http://twitter.com/gameloft or read our official blog at http://blog.gameloft.com/ ***