Enjoy a 100% authentic NFL game experience with real teams, real players and real action. Whether you’re are a fan of the Steelers, Cardinals or Cowboys, you can lead your favorite team through an entire season and battle for the ultimate prize: The Super Bowl.
- An officially licensed NFL videogame: Full teams rosters and the complete 2010 season 
- Intuitive controls: Move your player with the virtual pad, perform moves by touching the appropriate icon, and punch a hole through the other team’s play!
- A large selection of playbooks with over 200 plays to choose from
- 3D graphics worthy of the best handled console simulations with players and stadiums entirely modeled in 3D
- Audio commentary during the match
Don’t play football – live it.